northstudio.com 2018-12-09

# Privacy Policy | North Studio

We at North Studio (northStudio inc. and our affiliates) are committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy applies to our Website ([www.northstudio.com](https://www.northstudio.com/)). This Privacy Policy governs our data collection, processing and usage practices. By using the Website, you consent to the data practices described in this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with the data practices described in this Privacy Policy, you should not use the Website.

We periodically update this Privacy Policy. We encourage you to review this Privacy Policy periodically.

## 1\. Important Information

1.1. Changes to this Privacy Policy

We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time by posting a new version online. You should check this page occasionally to review any changes. If we make any material changes we will notify you by posting the revised Privacy Policy on our Website. This helps you to always be aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances, if any, it is disclosed. Your continued use of the Website and/or continued provision of Personal Information to us will be subject to the terms of the then-current Privacy Policy.

1.2. Contact Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or our treatment of the information you provide us, please write to us by email at [info@northstudio.com](mailto:info@northstudio.com) or by mail to 301-771 Vernon Ave, Victoria, BC, V8X 5A7, Attn: Privacy.

## 2\. Information We Collect

2.1. When You Visit our Website

You are free to explore the Website without providing any information about yourself. When you visit the Website, we collect Navigational Information.

2.2. “Personal Information”

This refers to any information that you voluntarily submit to us and that identifies you personally, including contact information, such as your name, e-mail address, company name, address, phone number, and other information about yourself or your business. Personal Information can also include information about any transactions, both free and paid, that you enter into on the Websites, and information about you that is available on the internet, such as from Facebook, LinkedIn, Twitter and Google, or publicly available information that we acquire from service providers.

2.3. “Navigational Information”

This refers to information about your computer and your visits to this website such as your IP address, geographical location, browser type, referral source, length of visit and pages viewed. Please see the “Navigation Information” section below.

2.4. Information About Children

The Websites are not intended for or targeted at children under 13, and we do not knowingly or intentionally collect information about children under 13. If you believe that we have collected information about a child under 13, please contact us at [info@northstudio.com](mailto:info@northstudio.com), so that we may delete the information.

## 3\. How We Use Information We Collect

3.1. Compliance with Our Privacy Policy

We use the information we collect only in compliance with this Privacy Policy.

3.2. We Never Sell Personal Information

We will never sell your Personal Information to any third party.

3.3. Use of Personal Information

In addition to the uses identified elsewhere in this Privacy Policy, we may use your Personal Information to: (a) improve your browsing experience by personalizing the Website; (b) send information to you which we think may be of interest to you by post, email, or other means; (c) send you marketing communications relating to our business or the businesses of carefully-selected third parties which we think may be of interest to you, and (d) provide other companies with statistical information about our users — but this information will not be used to identify any individual user. We may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, we do not transfer your unique Personal Information to the third party. In addition, we may share data with trusted partners to contact you based on your request to receive such communications, help us perform statistical analysis, or provide customer support. Such third parties are prohibited from using your Personal Information except for these purposes, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

3.4. Use of Navigational Information

We use Navigational Information to operate and improve the Website. We may also use Navigational Information alone or in combination with Personal Information to provide you with personalized information about North Studio.

3.5. Customer Testimonials and Comments

We post customer testimonials and comments on our Website, which may contain Personal Information. We obtain each customer’s consent via email prior to posting the customer’s name and testimonial.

3.6. Use of Credit Card Information

If you give us credit card information, we use it solely to check your financial qualifications and collect payment from you. We use a third-party service provider to manage credit card processing. This service provider is not permitted to store, retain, or use information you provide except for the sole purpose of credit card processing on our behalf.

3.7. Service Providers

We may employ other companies and people to provide services to visitors to our Website and our customers and may need to share your information with them to provide information, products or services to you. Examples may include removing repetitive information from prospect lists, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, processing credit card payments, supplementing the information you provide us in order to provide you with better service, and providing customer service. In all cases where we share your information with such agents, we explicitly require the agent to acknowledge and adhere to our privacy and customer data handling policies.

3.8. Security of your Personal Information

We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your Personal Information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. We secure the Personal Information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When sensitive Personal Information (such as a credit card number and/or geo-location data) is collected on our Website and/or transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.

3.9. Social Media Features

Our Website includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button and Widgets, such as the Share This button or interactive mini-programs that run on our site. These features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our sites, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Website. This Privacy Policy does not apply to these features.  Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy and other policies of the companies providing them.

3.10. External Websites

Our Website provides links to other websites. We do not control, and are not responsible for, the content or practices of these other websites. Our provision of such links does not constitute our endorsement of these other websites, their content, their owners, or their practices. This Privacy Policy does not apply to these other websites, which are subject to any privacy and other policies they may have.

3.11. Public Forums

We offer publicly accessible blogs. Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose any information through our public message boards, blogs, or forums, this information may be collected and used by others. We will correct or delete any information you have posted on the Website if you so request, as described in “Opting Out and Unsubscribing” below.

3.12. Retention of Personal Information

We retain Personal Information that you provide us as long as we consider it potentially useful in contacting you about our services, and then we securely delete the information. We will delete this information from the servers at an earlier date if you so request, as described in “Opting Out and Unsubscribing” below.

3.13. Corporate Events

If we (or our assets) are acquired by another company, whether by merger, acquisition, bankruptcy or otherwise, that company would receive all information gathered by North Studio on the Website.

3.14. Compelled Disclosure

We reserve the right to use or disclose your Personal Information if required by law or if we reasonably believe that use or disclosure is necessary to protect our rights or to comply with a law, court order, or legal process.

## 4\. Navigational Information

4.1. Cookies

We use “cookies” to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web server. Cookies are not used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a Web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize pages on our Website, a cookie helps us to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. When you return to the same Website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the customized features.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Website. North Studio keeps track of the pages you visit within North Studio, in order to determine what portion of the North Studio Website is the most popular or most used. This data is used to deliver customized content and promotions within the North Studio Website Service to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.

4.2. Log Files

We may collect demographic information, such as your postal code, age, gender, preferences, interests and favorites using log files that are not associated with your name or other personally identifying information. There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by us. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used by North Studio to provide general statistics regarding use of the North Studio Website. For these purposes, we do link this automatically-collected data to Personal Information such as name, email address, address, and phone number.

4.3. Clear Gifs (Web Beacons/Web Bugs)

We employ a software technology called clear gifs (a.k.a. Web Beacons/Web Bugs), that help us better manage the Website by informing us what content is effective.  Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of Web users. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user’s computer hard drive, clear gifs are embedded invisibly on Web pages or in emails and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. We use clear gifs in our HTML-based emails to let us know which emails have been opened by recipients. This allows us to gauge the effectiveness of certain communications and the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns. We tie the information gathered by clear gifs in emails to our customers’ Personal Information. If you would like to opt-out of these emails, please see “Opting Out and Unsubscribing”.

4.4. Flash Cookies and Other Third Party Tracking Technologies

The Adobe Flash Player (and similar applications) use technology to remember settings, preferences and usage similar to browser cookies but these are managed through a different interface than the one provided by your Web browser. This technology creates locally stored objects that are often referred to as “Flash cookies.” North Studio does not use Flash cookies.

4.5. Third Party Tracking Technologies

The use of cookies and web beacons by any tracking utility company is not covered by our privacy statement.  We do not have access or control over these third party tracking technologies

## 5\. Opting Out and Unsubscribing

5.1. Reviewing, Correcting and Removing Your Personal Information

If you provide us with your Personal Information, you have the following rights with respect to that information:

  * To review the user information that you have supplied to us
  * To request that we correct any errors, outdated information, or omissions in user information that you have supplied to us
  * To request that your user information not be used to contact you
  * To request that your user information be removed from any solicitation list that we use
  * To request that your user information be deleted from our records
  * To opt out of being solicited by North Studio or third parties

To exercise any of these rights, please contact us at [info@northstudio.com](mailto:info@northstudio.com) or by mail to North Studio, 301-771 Vernon Ave, Victoria, BC, V8X 5A7, Attention: Privacy. We will promptly change, correct, or delete your information and notify you of the action we have taken.

5.2. To Unsubscribe From Our Communications

You may unsubscribe from our marketing communications by clicking on the “unsubscribe” link located on the bottom of our e-mails, or by sending us an email at [info@northstudio.com](mailto:info@northstudio.com), or by sending us postal mail to North Studio, 301-771 Vernon Ave, Victoria, BC, V8X 5A7, Attention: Privacy. Customers cannot opt out of receiving transactional emails related to their account with us.
